CURRICULUM VITAE

Personal Details

Name Muhammad Baber Ali khan Address A-13 Bhayani View Block M

North Nazimabad Karachi74700 Pakistan

D.O.B. 7th April 1979.

Telephone +923332409514 /+923482233775

Email infobaber.khan@gmail.com

National Tax No 3727226-8



Career Summary

Date: Nov 2019 - till date, as " Admin Supervisor (Night Shift) in "Ibne Sina Hospital".

Working as, a " Night Admin Incharge / Supervisor" Night Shift.

Date: Oct 2018 – till August 2019, as "Administrator" in "Rajkot Memon Hospital" 50 years old hospital, running again under supervision of "Rajkot Memon Association.

• Worked as, a "Administrator".

Date: Oct 2017 - till August 2018, as "Admin Officer" in "Concept Advertisers"

• Worked as, a "Admin Officer".

Date: March 2016 - June 2017, BANK ALFALAH LTD "Officer". (Contractual Basis).

 Worked as Officer Recovery in litigation dept credit cards consumer finance center under reporting of RRM.

Date: August 2014 – October 2015, "Manager International Recoveries" with BILKISH ASSOCIATES Under reporting of overseas banker and principle offices in INDIA & UAE.

Worked as "Manager International Recovery".

Date: **January 2010–December 2013 MCB BANK LTD "Officer"** Under Reporting of Senior Recovery Manager RR**M.(Contractual Basis).**

• Worked as Officer Recovery for PIL & credit cards under reporting of RRM.

Date: March 2007–December 2009, Officer and Supervisor Recovery Credit Cards BANK ALFALAH LTD. (Contractual Basis).

 Worked as Officer Recovery consumer finance center and a team supervisor in recovery for credit cards.

Date: June2002 - December 2006, "Officer" under direct reporting of Administration in DR ZIAUDDIN HOSPITAL Head Office.

Worked as Front Officer.

Education.

MatriculationScience1994 3rd grade Karachi BoardIntermediatecommerce1996 3rd grade Govt Premier CollegeGraduationBachelor of Commerce2001 & 2015 2nd div Federal Urdu UniversityMastersMasters of Commerce2016 in process Federal Urdu University

PC Skills Word – Intermediate

Excel - Intermediate

PowerPoint (good command over networking & windows)

Internet and email with English Urdu Drafting

Languages.

Fluent in English and Urdu with good drafting.

Internal software's.

Foxpro2.6	(Offline)
Visual Basic	(Offline)
Card Pro Version 4	(Online)
Card Pro Version 5	(Online)
CWX	(Online)
CTL	(Online)
SYMBOLS	(Online)
BCMS	(Online)
SAP	(Online)

Training Courses.

Time Management Legal Environment for Consumer Finance Credit Cycle Legal Environment and its Impact on Consumer Banking Cash Management & Vigilance Overview

References. Will furnish upon request.

I have all the "Clearance / Experience letters and Educational Documents.

